Here I am again.
Really? Are you sure?
Slap!
Imagine how much we'll save on our food bill!
This is great! Thanks so much!
We pulled out all the stops for New Year's, so we're a little low on our food money.
But now we can have all kinds of delicious food again! This is great!
Piping hot!
We already finished with dinner earlier. They're just leftovers, but I hope it'll do.
It's delicious! This egg rice is so good!
Wee-Wei, stay here! I want you to snuggle with Mama tonight!
What a great idea! Why don't we have a slumber party, Ray?
I can't. I have to go back to my place tonight.
Why, Ray? Mama wants you to stay here!
Why? Why, Ray? Why? Why?
Wee, Momo...
Momo...
I'm sorry...
It's just I've got a match coming up that I can't lose.
that I can't lose. It's important.
I have to go home now so I can study and prepare.
Study and prepare? Does Rei have a test?
Yes. A big test.
I have to show my opponent. I have what it takes.
I've trained hard enough to make it this far.
Momo. Huh?
Don't you have something to say to Rei?
To Rei?
But Rei has a test and he has to study.
Yeah. And what do we say when we want to support someone?
Go tell him to do your best.
Listen, Rei. Do your best!
Right.
You've got it.
I am joking so you give me two hours.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
We've kind of first arrived in the day.
We are going to meet now.
We're going to meet today of the times of the week green.
That time he got
Well, what are you trying to do here for the Faster-BA sophisticated test
Thank you.
All right.
Time to go.
After that day, I spotted Kiriyama just once at Shogi Hall.
He was making copies of Shogi game records.
I was going to say hello.
But changed my mind when I saw the look on his face.
He'd been gathering game records, but only for Shimada Eighth Den and Goto Ninth Den.
Those two and no one else.
Huh, that little punk.
Well, that certainly pisses me off.
Wow, what a total jerk.
He didn't bother to check my game records.
He expects to crush Mr. Shimada, then move right on to Goto.
Who the hell does he think he is?
I just don't see it.
I can't see myself beating Goto and then facing Mr. Shimada.
But nevertheless, I get it.
That's just the way it is.
Kiriyama has a vision.
It's not a figment of his imagination or selfish in any way.
We're professionals.
And no matter how it makes us feel,
we always measure our own ability with brutal precision.
That's the sort of honesty that makes you a pro.
Some people go in thinking they may end up winning.
And because of that, there's a good chance that they will win.
But I don't have that vision.
A vision of beating Goto and facing Mr. Shimada myself.
That's just something I don't see.
That being said,
having the tenacity to fight for victory is also part of a pro's job.
Good thing I happen to be a professional.
Goto favors the static rook and bear in the cave.
I'll use the pinwheel to counter that.
But if Goto's style is heavy and stiff,
I'll be flexible and light like a feather.
Let's have a good game.
To be right here,
let's have a good game.
Let's have a good game.
Okay.
Thank you.
Goto will play a firm defense and target me with a single massive strike.
If that attack hits me, it's over.
I can't let my concentration slip for a second.
But I'm ready to face him.
Victory or defeat is never guaranteed before the match begins.
That doesn't happen in matches between pros.
Looks like we got some pretty nasty rain clouds.
Actually, on the news they're saying we're in for snow tonight.
No wonder.
I thought it was colder than usual.
Just how strong is this guy?
I keep wounding him, but he won't collapse.
There aren't any openings.
I've drawn so much blood, but he hasn't flinched.
But my moves aren't getting very far right now.
Finally, he's started his attack.
He's sacrificed his rook.
What the hell is he doing?
What does he see?
He's attacking me with tremendous force.
I can't hold the line.
Pitch black water is pouring in on me.
I can't breathe.
I'm being dragged down to the bottom.
What can I do?
There's nothing left.
Nothing.
I lost the match.
You were light.
But still, a bit too heavy.
After I took bishop to 2-6,
you defended with gold to 5-2.
You should have gone up to gold 6-3 instead.
That move didn't fit with your style.
Lightness is your creed, isn't it?
Next time, be decisive.
That was pathetic.
Not only was it a complete defeat,
but I had to sit through his lecture as well.
What's the deal with that bassy voice?
It's so deep.
How old is he?
Like 41?
I wonder if I'll be able to project that kind of intensity in 10 years.
I bet that he gets all the girls.
Oh, it pisses me off just thinking about it.
All righty then.
Let's see what the night has in store for me now.
Option A.
If it goes in, I drink my cares away at the pub.
Option B.
If I miss, I go home, get under the covers, and cry.
Hey.
Stop, stop, stop.
Gas.
No way! I can't believe it! Option C!
What?
What should I do?
All right already! I get it!
It's okay. Stop crying.
We'll start again. You and me both. From square one.
Hey. You're looking well.
That's too bad, isn't it?
Interesting.
If we keep this up, the two of us will be going head to head in no time.
Well, I'll be looking forward to that.
It should be a little more interesting than beating you with my bare hands.
Ah. That's right.
I have a message I want you to pass on to your old man for me.
It's about that girl that won't stop stalking me.
Tell him he really needs to get her off my back.
She's really cramping my style.
Got it.
He was goading me.
I know that.
But, there's no choice.
The next round starts today.
The only thing that matters now is winning.
Kai Shimada, 8th Den.
Five years in Class A.
I've been looking over his game records.
But, it's weird.
Nothing really stands out.
Tactics he's good at.
Weaknesses.
There's nothing unique.
I've never played against them before.
But, I remember him.
Back in grade school,
I attended a children's shogi tournament.
And, he was there as a guest speaker.
I remember he was tall and thin.
And, spoke quietly.
I was on a winning streak and didn't really pay attention.
Guess he didn't leave much of an impression on me.
Instead of playing to win,
he's someone who plays not to lose.
Games against people like that are usually long and drawn out.
That's my weakness.
I can't let it get to me.
Or you'll eat me alive.
Stay calm.
It's a very special gift.
From Goto.
I can't lose this match.
No matter what.
I made the first move of the match.
A double fortress.
It's been all defense so far.
Time to attack.
Let's go.
Rook to 5-2.
Is he going to block everything?
Fine.
Then in that case...
He moved gold back.
He's moving his rook?
Then so will I.
I don't get it.
This is hard to play.
When in doubt...
Protect the king.
All right.
Protect?
Wait a second.
That doesn't make sense.
I was supposed to be attacking.
And yet...
Somewhere along the way, I started defending.
What is this?
How did it get so bad?
I didn't...
Even make...
Any mistakes.
How did this happen?
This...
This intensity...
I'm out of moves.
I can't attack.
Damn it.
I feel like...
What is that?
Ah, took you long enough. Finally caught your eye, huh?
Mr. Shimada!
What'd you come here for, kiddo? I know that you don't have any matches today.
Sorry to bother you.
How's your fever been? You still feel pretty warm. You gotta take care of yourself. Your promotion is on the line, you know.
You already promised us that you wouldn't overdo it, both me and your teacher. In exchange, we promised that we wouldn't tell anyone.
Right. I'll go home and lie down right now. I'm sorry, sir.
Good. Well, me too. Sorry for getting on your case like that. I'm just really surprised to see you here.
So then, why are you here? Is there something you need to talk about? What's on your mind?
Well, I guess there is something. I want you...
Huh?
I want you to crush Kiriyama's pride in your next Shogi match!
Ah, boy. I was wondering what he was going to say.
That's asking an awful lot.
Uh-uh.
All right, then.
Well, guess we should continue.
I'll see you.
who wants to have a cold lunch when they're totally depressed go on otherwise you'll lose
half your hit points so he needs to make the first move then what do i do who the hell even knows
anymore okay why don't we replay from this point in the match march comes in like a lion at long
last mr shimata's here he's playing a match make sure to watch it that's an order
this is